Guide to the Stanford University, Planning Office, Records SC0486
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Planning Office, records
1945-2013
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Spencer, Eldridge T.
Stanford University. Planning Office
SC0486
102.5 Linear Feet
The records of the Planning Office date back to its orgins in 1945 and include correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, studies, surveys, maps, and plans.
Separated Materials note
Photographs originally part of accession ARCH-1990-052 were removed and catalogued separately as PC0062, Planning Office Photographs; please see the guide to that collection for further details.
Scope and Contents Note
The records of the Planning Office date back to its orgins in 1945 and include correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, studies, surveys, maps, and plans. The majority of the plans in this collection are 8 by 10 inch photographic reproductions of larger items, prepared for use in reports and publications. For larger format plans and drawings, please consult the University Archives Architectural Drawings Collection.
Historical Note
The Planning Office was officially organized in 1945 under the directorship of Eldridge T. Spencer. In addition to overseeing the architectural aspects of the campus, the office was also responsible for overseeing land use and traffic circulation. With the growth of the campus, the administration of planning activities has undergone several renovations. In 1972 the office was renamed Facilities Planning, Construction and Utilization; in 1978 it was known as Facilities Planning and Construction. In the 1980s these elements were handled by two offices: Facilities Project Management and the Planning Office.
Other directors represented in these records include Spencer's successor, Harry Sanders, and Philip C. Williams, who became director in 1975.
Access Restrictions:
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Arrangement note
Materials are arranged by accession.
Custodial History
The materials were received from the Planning Office in numerous transfers between 1987 and 2010.
Stanford University -- General subdivision--Buildings.;; Spencer, Eldridge T.; Spencer, Eldridge T.; Sanders, Harry L.; Williams, Philip C.; Sanders, Harry L.; Stanford University. Planning Office
- Records, Accession ARCH-1987-036
  - College Terrace Traffic Problem (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1987-060
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management 1946-71 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management 1962-63 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management 1965-66 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management Feb. 1968 - April 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management May 1974 - Dec. 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management Jan. 1976 - Oct. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Planning Office procedures - Project Management Nov. 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Projects - PACE February 1961 - Sept. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Projects - PACE October 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Projects - Post PACE (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Projects - Lists and priorities Jan. 1944 - Oct. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Projects - Lists and priorities Jan. 1960 - Nov. 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Projects - Lists and priorities Jan. 1964 - May 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Projects - Lists and priorities June 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Publicity - News releases (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Publications - subscriptions July 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate housing study, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Planning Office work: other than procedures, Sept. 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Planning Office work: other than procedures, Jan. 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Planning Office work: plant renovation fund (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Planning Office work: OSHA violations corrections - funding (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Planning Office questionnaire, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Procedures: general memoranda - miscellaneous Dec. 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Portraits of the Presidents (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1987-067
  - Near West Campus Plan, 1987; Historic Values Index, July 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Land Use Plan - 1980; Vegetation Management; Inner Quad Courtyard (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lighting Plan, 1985 West Campus Region Plan, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lake Lagunita Direct Seeding of Oaks, 1985 "Ears of the Oval," 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Foothills Region Plan, 1987 Athletics, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1987-075
  - Planning Regional (Palo Alto): "CS" Zoning (Box 1, Folder 1-10)
  - Planning Regional (Palo Alto): Proposed Zoning Regulations (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Planning Regional (Palo Alto): Draft Zoning Ordinance Text (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Zoning (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - Location of Academic Department (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Condemnations, Easements, Sales (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - PEP-AECM - Negotiating (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Trailers & Temporary Buildings (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - SLAC (Box 2, Folder 5-end)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1988-093
  - Progress Report. Eldridge Spencer, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Survey. Eldridge Spencer, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Survey. Eldridge Spencer, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Planning Report, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Site Plans for Contemporary American Universities (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Development of Circulation and Parking, April 1958; Report on Master Plan, June 1954; Report on Master Plan for Campus Land Use, April 1956. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Committee: Agenda & Minutes, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Parking and Traffic Committee, Minutes, 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Master Plan for a University's Growth, Architectural Records, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Master Plan of Exterior Lighting, April 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Police Parking Maps (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Plans and Designs: Master Parking Plan, Parking Study. (Box 3 (OS))
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1988-115
  - Statistics: Parking - on campus (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan: Parking - general (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Visitor Parking Maps (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Registrations: Automobile Circulation (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Registrations: 1978-79 Campus Parking Permits (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Registrations: 1977-78 Campus Parking Permits (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Registrations: 1976-77 Campus Parking Permits (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Registrations: 1975-76 Campus Parking Permits (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Registrations: Statistics (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Parking Program:, 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Registrations: Statistics (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Parking Analysis (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kiosk Disk (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annexation Study (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Misc. Planning Office Material (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Robicheck Memorial, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Study of Annexation of Stanford Lands to the City of Palo Alto, Nov. 16, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Maps/Drawings re: Parking and circulation (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Palm Tree Relocation -, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Main Quad Plants (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Land Development Annual Report (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Questions and Answers About Stanford Land Use -, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Planning (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Land Use - Master Plans - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Places to Live at Stanford: Survey and Proposal (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1989-215
  - Historical data sheets, (fairly complete information on nearly all campus buildings as of 1950-60), circa 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Historical data sheets (different type from folder 1; not as complete) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Historical information on the campus, campus lands, and buildings (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Music Building, final report, Charles Luckman Associates, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Original copy for Personnel and Facilities open house notice (includes half-tone of the offices in the Old Pavilion) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - McLellan & Copenhagen, Vol. I: Planning Study prepared for Department of Biological Sciences, September 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - McLellan & Copenhagen, Vol. II: Building Program Study prepared for Department of Biological Sciences, September 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - McLellan & Copenhagen, Vol. I: Planning Study and Vol. II: Building Program (draft) prepared for Department of Biological Sciences, August 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1986-165
  - Colored photostats of survey of Stanford properties by Punnett, Parez, and Hutcheson, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan negative, campus lands, April 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photostat negatives and printing plates for "Campaign Plant Components,", 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Text placards from Planning Office displays, including one from photographs by Moffat Hancock, 1958 and undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Negative prints and photostats of various planning maps and miscellaneous architectural drawings, 1950-1961 and undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1990-052
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): publicity drawing Campus Drive past Medical School 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): Science Quad 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): pedestrian areas around main quad 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): Circulation Study #2 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): alignment study for peripheral road 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): peripheral road study in relation to land use 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): peripheral road study in relation to student union 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): existing traffic circulation 1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): traffice circulation study, stage 1, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): traffice circulation study, stage 2, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): traffice circulation study, stage 3, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Circulation and parking (largely maps): existing parking on campus 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): area needed for 10-year exp. program at current densities 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): study of undergrauate clusters; architectural renderings by John Carl Warnecke 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): campus land lease map 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): proposed graudate men's, study of, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): Crothers studies 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): Stern Hall expansion studies 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): existing men's (ownership status) 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): existing men's (locations & capacities) 1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): campus land subdivisions map 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Housing (drawings, perspectives, maps): key plan of proposed types & distribution 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): undergraduate library 1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): currentt & proposed bulding projects on Stanford campus 1958 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): buffer zone study 1955 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): additional building and praking needs based on current enrollment 1954 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): Master Plan Report Advisiory Committee [text negatives] 1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): chart of growth 1953-54 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): land use & circulation 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): neighborhood development site plan 1949 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): land development 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): campus development 1945 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): utilization of classroom seating space 1949-50 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): utilization of classroom seating space 1945-48 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Planning Studies (mostly drawings and maps): utilization of classroom seating space pre 1945 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Other Universities (mostly drawings and maps): faculty swimming pool, Lehigh Country Club 1954 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Other Universities (mostly drawings and maps): Baptist Theological Seminary, Strawberry Point, Marin County, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Other Universities (mostly drawings and maps): campuses (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Historical: printing neg for Olmsted's Plan of 1888 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Historical: printing neg for Olmsted's perspective of 1888 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Historical: maps and aerial photos (some in negative) of Stanford ownerships (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Land Use (mostly drawings and maps): Ampex Site 1960 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Land Use (mostly drawings and maps): study of proposed uses in restricted area 1950 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Land Use (mostly drawings and maps): maps and plans, miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration study 4-D4 Sheets 1 and 2, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration study 4-D3 Sheets 1 and 2, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration study 4A Sheets 1-3, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration Building remodel 1948 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration study 1-E Sheets 1-3, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad I - Administration Study - Site Plan Schemes 1-4, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Music Building, preliminaries, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Music at Stanford brochure (includes correspondence of Eldridge Spencer) 1954 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Music listening, Ann Clare Brokaw memorial, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Journalistic Studies - Schho of (Beaubaire Bldg.) 1952 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Journalistic Studies perspective 1952 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, McKay & Somps topographic survey 1957 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, site and utilities plan, Feb. 1952 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, floor plans, sheets 1 and 2, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center [site plan] 1949 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, Tresidder Memorial, August 1949 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, perspective 1952 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Student Activities Center, plot plan 1952 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Petrography Bldg. alterations, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad II - Health Center 1949 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Hoover Library, preliminary perspective 1941 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Stanford Library & Library Quad, library floor plans, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Stanford Library & Library Quad, plans 1925 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Stanford Library & Library Quad, plans 1941 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Stanford Library & Library Quad, plans 1954 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Stanford Library & Library Quad, plans 1959 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad III - Undergraduate Library - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Proposed mineral engineering building, plans & elevations 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - High Energy Physics Laboratory extension 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Microwave Laboratory plan 1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - proposed IBM building 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - science quad 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - proposed mineral sceince building, plan and elevation 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - geophysics building [correspndence, no plans] 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Electronic Research Laboratory perspective 1952 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Electronic Research Laboratory floor plan 1952 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Proposed School of Mineral Sciences Study 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Physics at Stanford [negatives of text, plans] 1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Physics Quad Studies, Gardner Dailey, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - Chemistry at Stanford [negatives of text, plans] 1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school studies 1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school study [photograph of model for cover of report] (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school (proposed) 1953 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school redevelopment scheme G., September 1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school studies 1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical school redevelopment - scheme I (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad IV - medical linear accelerator 1953 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall completion 1958 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall perspective 1954 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall addition plot plans 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall siete and eleveations 1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall group perspective of terrace 1947 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall group floor plan 1947 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Stern Hall group plot plan 1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Wilbur Hall site plan and floor plans 1954 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Wilbur Hall final perspective 1953 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Wilbur Hall perspective 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Crothers Hall perspectives 1946 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Crothers Hall addition plans 1952 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VI - Encina Hall remodeling 1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VII - proposed Stauffer Chemical Buildings, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad VIII - Music development studies, 1946-52 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad X - Married student housing [site plan] (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad X - Married student housing and Pine Hill site map, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Drawings and plans for studies or projects: Quad X - Married student housing [plans, drawings] 1957 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Road Project files: Campus Drive extension, 1978-82 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Road Project files: Santa Teresa Street extension, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Road Project files: Lomita Drive, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Road Project files: Circulation roads and walks, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Road Project files: Circulation general 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Planning Office Reports: Planning report housing, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Planning Office Reports: Planning report housing, 1945 (different version) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Planning Office Reports: A Coordinated plan for the University, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Planning Office Reports: A Coordinated plan for the University, 1947 (different version) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Planning Office Reports: A Coordinated plan for the University, 1947 (different version) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Classroom space utilization, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Student housing report, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Planning at Stanford, 1952 [2 copies (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Studies for graduate men's housing, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Residence hall for men, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Interim report - Stanford master plan; shopping center, industrial area, proposed residential development, Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Report on Master Plan, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Music at Stanford, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Physics at Stanford, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty housing, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Report on master plan for campus land use, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Student activities center for Stanford University, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Medical School site study [plans by Isadore and Zachary Rosenfield - Rex Whitaker Allen], 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Housing for married students at Stanford, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pine Hill residential area, Stanford University, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Summary report on married student housing, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Development of circulation and parking for the academic campus, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Places to live at Stanford [student housing], 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)